<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Project on Project ANR DT4CPS</title><link>https://dt4cps.fr/en/projet/</link><description>Recent content in Project on Project ANR DT4CPS</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 12:56:22 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dt4cps.fr/en/projet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Work package 3 : Méthodes et outils pour la commande et la reconfiguration</title><link>https://dt4cps.fr/en/projet/wp3/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 12:56:22 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://dt4cps.fr/en/projet/wp3/</guid><description>Objectives PB3: How can the Digital Twin enable the optimal utilization of a reconfigurable system&amp;rsquo;s flexibility?
A reconfigurable system often has the capability for reconfiguration, but it can be challenging to evaluate. The Digital Twin should be a decision support tool for reconfigurability, providing the operator with relevant indicators and a simulation of the consequences of reconfiguration. OB3: Exploit the Digital Twin of a CPS to identify potential reconfigurations and their consequences (in terms of production and energy).</description></item><item><title>Work package 2 : Garantir l’alignement des jumeaux </title><link>https://dt4cps.fr/en/projet/wp2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 12:56:19 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://dt4cps.fr/en/projet/wp2/</guid><description>Objectives PB2: How to ensure behavioral consistency and temporal synchronization between the Physical Twin and the Digital Twin?
The DT must exhibit behavior consistent with that of its physical twin. Temporally, an instance of the DT must be synchronized, while other instances of the DT can evolve at different time scales, both in the past and in the future from a chosen moment.
In a situation where the twins are not aligned, either behaviorally or temporally, questions arise such as: (i) Which twin should be updated?</description></item><item><title>Work Package 1 : Méthodologie pour la mise en place d’un JN multi-échelles</title><link>https://dt4cps.fr/en/projet/wp1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 12:56:16 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://dt4cps.fr/en/projet/wp1/</guid><description>Objectives PB1: How to test and validate a Digital Twin?
By definition, a CPS operates at multiple temporal and spatial scales. Therefore, it is necessary for the Digital Twin, itself defined as a set of models, to also operate in a multi-scale environment.
OB1: Propose a methodology for implementing a digital twin that integrates the models and data required by both the automation engineer (at the scale of a controller of a CPS) and the production engineer (at the scale of a line composed of CPS, i.</description></item><item><title>Work Package 4 : Cas d’usage, démonstrateur et expérimentations</title><link>https://dt4cps.fr/en/projet/wp4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 12:56:16 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://dt4cps.fr/en/projet/wp4/</guid><description>Objectives OB4: Each of the first three objectives will have its own specific use case for validating the results.
However, it seems necessary to have a benchmark/demonstrator that incorporates all the results obtained from the DT4CPS project through a final objective. Tasks Task 4.1: Definition of professions and activity analysis Deliverable D4.1: Analysis, descriptions, and prescriptions on individual and social usage patterns, instruments built in connection with the facets of professions, obstacles, dilemmas, and potentialities related to the Human-Machine system.</description></item></channel></rss>